Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Records UA090
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Master's program field project reports, 1981 -- 2021; UA090.003; 145 Digital Object(s); 3 Linear Feet
  - Arts, Culture, and Economic Development: Experiences in Boston and Beyond (Madison Park Field Project), 1999; UA090.003.003.00008; Beyene, Tina; Dobrowolski, Tania; Murphy, Tara; Rivera, Federico; Zucconi, Tanya; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 8)
    1999 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Arts, Culture, and Trade Roxbury Consortium
  - Chestnut Hill Reservoir: Water Quality Action Plan, 1999; UA090.003.003.00009; Byrne, Darcy; Crowley, Tyke; Frigoletto, Darah; Kelley, Jaime; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 9)
    1999 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Massachusetts Water Resource Authority (MWRA)
  - Making A Difference: Quantifying the Benefits of the Environmentally Preferable Products Procurement Program, 1999; UA090.003.003.00010; Levine, Trillium; Mitchell, Yvette; Pinheiro, Flavio; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 10)
    1999 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Massachusetts Operational Services Division
  - The State of Community Gardens in Somerville: An Examination of the Past and a Glimpse into the Future, 2000; UA090.003.003.00011; Evans, Tom; Filapek, Julie; Ralph, Dri; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 11)
    2000 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Somerville Conservation Committee
  - 99 Degrees in Collaboration with the Women's Statewide Legislative Network, 2000; UA090.003.003.00012; Maxwell, Heather; Verdun, Amy; Higginbotham, Nia; Aronson, Rachal; Lazeroff, Adrienne; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 0 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 12)
    2000 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Women's Statewide Legislative Network
  - Stormwater Pollution Prevention in an Ultra-Urban Setting, 2000; UA090.003.003.00013; Gardner, Kristin; Kelly, Nathan; Stelle, Marjorie; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 13)
    2000 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: City of Somerville, MA Department of Fisheries, Wildlife and Environmental Law Enforcement-Riverways Program, and the Alewife/Mystic River Advocates
  - A New Fenway Park? It's Not a Done Deal! Action Manual for Concerned Residents, 2000; UA090.003.003.00014; Davis, Joshua; Rearick, Whitney; Schwarz, Erica; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 14)
    2000 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Fenway CDC
  - Preserving the Scenic Character of Ipswich, Massachusetts, 2000; UA090.003.003.00015; Martin, Matthew; Muzzy, Wendy; Rodrigues, Kathi; Tajima, Kayo; Theut, Jodi; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 15)
    2000 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Town of Ipswich Planning Department
  - An Examination of Students' Experiences with Race and Diversity in the Tufts Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2000; UA090.003.003.00016; Argersinger, Erika; Bates, Tamara; Gandhi, Bindi; Martinez, Marty; Palazzolo, Tim; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 16)
    2000 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Tufts University Oversight Panel of the Task Force on Race
  - Success Measures Field Projects, 2000; UA090.003.003.00017; Durham, Laura; O'Neil, Emily; Wagner, Tanya; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 17)
    2000 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Development Leadership Network (DLN)
  - TCI Climate Change Awareness Plan, 2001; UA090.003.003.00018; Calahong, Jacqueline; Terry, Mojisola; Ohata, Aki; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 18)
    2001 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Tufts Climate Initiative
  - Tufts University Lincoln Filene Center Renovation Project, 2001; UA090.003.003.00019; Luftig, Jennifer; Sugai, Kayo; Brust, Jennifer; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 19)
    2001 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: University College of Citizenship and Public Service
  - Cambridge Sewer Separation/Alewife Brook Combined Sewer Overflow (CSO), 2001; UA090.003.003.00020; Fuligni, Danielle; Gardner, Aimee; Moore, David Richard; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 20)
    2001 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Mystic River Collaborative and Mystic River Watershed Association
  - Open Space Management Plan for the Town of Ipswich, 2001; UA090.003.003.00021; Blessinger, Amy; Gardner, Cameron; Herzfeld, Cornelia; Torres, Ryan; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 21)
    2001 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Town of Ipswich
  - Proposal Paper: Development of and Vision for the TUCC Resource Room, 2001; UA090.003.003.00022; Colon, Melvyn; Witten, Jon; Daly, Terese; Lefkowitz, Paul; O'Rourke, Kelly; Pannhorst, Kathleen; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 22)
    2001 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Tufts University Center for Children
  - TuftsNEN Homeless Youth Counting Project, 2002; UA090.003.003.00023; Roy, Pialee; Richardi, Kristina; Breindel, Harlan; Bonner, Jeff; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 23)
    2002 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: New England Network for Child and Family Services (NEN)
  - A Needs and Asset Evaluation in the South End/Lower Roxbury Neighborhoods, 2002; UA090.003.003.00024; Cupp, Sarah; Hall, Sarah; Hall, Susan; Mitchell, Christian; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 24)
    2002 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: South End/Lower Roxbury Youth Workers Alliance
  - Waste Materials Exchange at the Community Level: Building Readiness and Awareness, 2002; UA090.003.003.00025; du Moulin, Andrew; Radicci, Roberto; Teter, Wes; Wozniak, Marissa; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 25)
    2002 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Dudley Street Neighborhood Initiative (DSNI)
  - Growing Spaces in Urban Places: Community Economic Development in the Dudley Neighborhood, 2002; UA090.003.003.00026; Burton, Hannah; Chapdelaine, Katy; Gormly, Kate; Isaacs, Henry Aaron; Sprajcar, Jessica; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Closing the Gap: Building Wealth in Communities of Color Through Economic Development, 2002; UA090.003.003.00027; Dilday, Ayana; Hicks, Ana; Jackson, Sarah; Meyer, Jeff; Valente, Jesse; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 27)
    2002 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: United for a Fair Economy
  - Make Way for the Aggre-Gator: Helping Pool Consumer Demand for Green Power in Massachusetts, 2002; UA090.003.003.00028; Gellis, Victoria; Hengen, Mark; Veit, Cyndi; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 28)
    2002 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Mass Energy Group
  - Cool Medford: A Guide to Save the Planet from Your Couch, 2002; UA090.003.003.00029; Aguilera, Alejandro; Enoki, Takeshi; Taylor, Robin; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 29)
    2002 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: City of Medford, MA
  - Planning in Massachusetts: An Examination of the Inherent Challenges in the Existing Intergovernmental System, 2003; UA090.003.003.00030; Bottino, Gabriel; Kirkpatrick, Heather; Morgan, Diana; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 30)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Town of Marshfield
  - Environmental Health Community Mapping in Dorchester, 2003; UA090.003.003.00031; Centrella, Chris; Lautze, Jonathan; Viola, Christina; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 31)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Dorchester Environmental Health Council
  - Pioneer Institute: Its Influence on Massachusetts Mental Health Policy, 2003; UA090.003.003.00032; Baker, Jessie; Moksim, Julie; Jones, Lucille; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 32)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Pioneer Institute
  - The Spicket River Greenway: An Investigation of Parcels, Policies and Best Practices, 2003; UA090.003.003.00033; Crimmin, Darien; Lappin, Jennifer; Sherman, Kim; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 33)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Groundwork Lawrence
  - Town of Ipswich Housing Affordability Study, 2003; UA090.003.003.00034; Newman, Rachel; Sharples, David; Tighe, J. Rosie; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 34)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Town of Ipswich, MA
  - Helping Wounded Eagles Soar: A Needs Assessment of Mainstream Agencies Serving Native American Youth in New England, 2003; UA090.003.003.00035; Alger, Heather; Conrad, Sarah; Noel, Ketsia; Volk, Katherine; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 35)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: New England Network for Child, Youth and Family Services
  - The Inner Belt District: An Analysis of Surrounding Areas and Recommendations, 2003; UA090.003.003.00036; Channel, Joshua; Kollar, Daniel; Martin, David; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 36)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Somerville Chamber of Commerce
  - Biotechnology Development in Roxbury: Determining the Implications of the "Biotech Corridor", 2003; UA090.003.003.00037; Vega, Rosaura; Huntley, Ramsay; Ross, Heather; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 37)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Alternatives for Community and Environment Safety Net
  - Protection of Massachusetts Recharge Areas, 2003; UA090.003.003.00038; Lane, Courtney; McCrory, Marilyn; Moodie, James; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 38)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Massachusetts Executive Office of Environmental Affairs
  - Faith and Environmental Stewardship: Strategies for Area Religious Leaders to Engage in Environmental Efforts, 2003; UA090.003.003.00039; Hermann, Gabrielle; Jones, Matthew; Sasaki, Shotaro; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 39)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: City of Medford, MA
  - Zoning Regulations in the City of Lawrence and their Consequences on the Arlington Neighborhood, 2003; UA090.003.003.00040; Bandura, Ivanna; Martinez, Mariela; LoRusso, Karen Roth; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 40)
    2003 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Arlington Neighborhood Association, Inc. (ANA)
  - Beyond the Minimum: Stormwater Management in Ipswich, MA, 2004; UA090.003.003.00041; Bowman, Andrea; Olmsted, Dara; Whitmore, Kelley; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 41)
    2004 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Town of Ipswich, MA
  - Conserving Biodiversity in the Northeast: Atmospheric Desposition and Invasive Species, 2004; UA090.003.003.00042; Chilton, Eric; Grosshans, Jon; Larsen, John W.; Madsen, Karen; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 42)
    2004 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: The Nature Conservancy, Northeast Freshwaters Division, Boston, MA
  - Waterways Ordinances and Public Access Policies, 2004; UA090.003.003.00043; Alward, Brian; Curtis, Lara; Murphy, Susan; Neely, Dona; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 43)
    2004 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Everett Police Marine Division/Office of the Harbormaster
  - Asian Community Development Corporation (ACDC) Job Fair Improvement Analysis, 2004; UA090.003.003.00044; Barry, Shannon; Potsaid, Timothy; Saffari, Pardis; Schilz, Beau; Yamaguchi, Yukiko; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 44)
    2004 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Asian Community Development Corporation (ACDC)
  - Tent City Apartments: Considerations for Cooperative Ownership, 2004; UA090.003.003.00045; Brooks, Brandy; Huggins, Barbara; Kambli, Shubhada; LeWinter, Dana; Torrie, Yve; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 45)
    2004 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Tent City Corporation
  - Boston University's National Biocontainment Laboratory Economic Opportunity or Environmental Injustice?, 2004; UA090.003.003.00046; Hatic, Halida; Henninger, Kirsten; Ponce-Silen, Carlos; Stallings, Ericka; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 46)
    2004 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Alternatives for Community and Environment
  - "Better Than or Equal To": Design Alternatives for the Washington Street Corridor, 2004; UA090.003.003.00047; Knopsnyder, Heather; Telegen, Joanne; Fillis, Danielle; Dugan, Thomas; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 47)
    2004 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Washington Street Corridor Coalition
  - Urban Community Gardens and Orchards: A Maintenance Guide for Dudley Neighbors Inc., 2004; UA090.003.003.00048; Dunn, Kathleen; Mondazzi, Michelle; Rennie, Gary; Suprock, Julia; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 48)
    2004 M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Dudley Street Neighborhood Initiative (DSNI)
  - More Than a Roof Over Their Heads: A Qualitative Evaluation of Transitional Living Programs, 2004; UA090.003.003.00049; Bartlett, Megan; Copeman, Abby; Golin, Joshua; Miller, Daniel; Needle, Elana; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 49)
    M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: New England Network for Child, Youth and Family Services
  - Empowering New and Long-term Residents in Somerville's Linden Street Neighborhood, UA090.003.003.00050; Holtzman, David; Gordon, Ilana; Ozkul, Cagatay; Marzi, Susanne; Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 3, Folder 50)
    M.A. in Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning Field Project. Client: Somerville Community Corporation
- Additional accessions, 1985 -- 1989; UA090.004
  - Urban and Environmental Policy, 1985 -- 1989; UA090-001 (Box 1)
- Syllabi, 1978 -- 2014; UA090.000015; 2.5 Linear Feet 2 record cartons and 1 document box
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning staff, 2019, accession UA-2020-002.
  This series is arranged by course number.
  This series contains syllabi from Department of Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning courses.
  - UEP 151, circa 1980; UA090.000016 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - UEP 153S: Urban Studies and Planning, Summer 1985; UA090.000017 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - UEP 161: Writing and Public Speaking, Summer 1991 -- Summer 2013; UA090.000018 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - UEP 162B: Quantitative Research Methods, Summer 1994 -- Summer 2006; UA090.000019 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - UEP 165B: Developing Sustainable Communities, circa 2000; UA090.000020 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - UEP 166A/UEP 294: International Environmental Policy, Summer 1993 -- 2007; UA090.000021 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - UEP 170B: Globalization and the Environment, Summer 2003; UA090.000022 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - UEP 172B: Social Marketing in Policy and Program Management, Summer 2004 -- Summer 2007; UA090.000023 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - UEP 174A: Clean Air and Clean Water, Summer 2005 -- Summer 2013; UA090.000024 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - UEP 178: Globalization and Environment, Summer 2003; UA090.000025 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - UEP 180B: Policy and Planning, Summer 2004; UA090.000026 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - UEP 182A: Social Policies for Children and Families, Summer 2003 -- Fall 2008; UA090.000027 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - UEP 185A: Environmental NGO's and Public Policy Change, Summer 2000; UA090.000028 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - UEP 191A/B: Philanthropy and Fundraising, Summer 1999 -- Summer 2002; UA090.000029 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - UEP 191A: Philanthropy and Fundraising, Summer 1996 -- Summer 2005; UA090.000030 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - UEP 191AC: Critical Resource Area Protection, Summer 1997 -- Summer 1998; UA090.000031 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - UEP 191C: Applied Watershed Management, Summer 1998; UA090.000032 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - UEP 191CA: Introduction to Real Estate Financial Analysis, Summer 1998; UA090.000033 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - UEP 193AB: Environmental Economics, Summer 2000; UA090.000034 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - UEP 193B: Biotechnology and Society, Summer 1994 -- Summer 1996; UA090.000035 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - UEP 193B: Environmental Ethics, Summer 1999; UA090.000036 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - UEP/CE 193BW: Wetland Management and Field Analysis, Summer 2001 -- Summer 2002; UA090.000037 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - UEP 193S: Hazardous Waste Management, Summer 1985; UA090.000038 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - UEP 194-04: Climate Change: The Legal Response, Fall 2014; UA090.000039 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - UEP 195B: Biological Diversity and Conservation Strategies, Summer 1989; UA090.000040 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - UEP 293B: Coastal and Ocean Resources Management, circa 1993; UA090.000041 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - UEP 294-08: Planning for Low Impact Development, Summer 2008 -- Spring 2009; UA090.000042 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - UEP 294-BA: The Nuclear Power Option, Summer 2009 -- Summer 2012; UA090.000043 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - UEP 294-B: Jobs that Work: Designing Employment Strategies for Today's Communities, Summer 2010; UA090.000044 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - UEP 094: Environmental Policy, Planning and Politics, Spring 2009; UA090.000045 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - PS 142/UEP 142: Seminar on Interest Groups and Democratic Theory, Fall 1991 -- Fall 2000; UA090.000046 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - UEP 181: Homelessness in America, Spring 2002 -- Spring 2013; UA090.000047 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - UEP 182/CS 182: Social Policies for Children and Families, Fall 2001 -- Fall 2008; UA090.000048 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - UEP 188: Seminar on Government and the Family, Spring 1998 -- Spring 2004; UA090.000049 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - UEP 200: Land Use Planning I: Non-Regulatory Tools and Techniques, Spring 2002 -- Fall 2006; UA090.000050 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - UEP 201: Land Use Planning II, Spring 2005 -- Spring 2013; UA090.000051 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - UEP 203/PHIL 173: Ethics and the Environment, Spring 1996 -- Spring 1997; UA090.000052 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - UEP 205/PS 117: Urban and Environmental Planning and Design, Fall 2001 -- Fall 2012; UA090.000053 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - UEP 207: Environmental Law and Enforcement, Fall 2002 -- Fall 2011; UA090.000054 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - UEP 213: Housing Policy, Spring 1999 -- Fall 2010; UA090.000055 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - UEP 215: Legal Frameworks of Social Policy, circa 2004 -- 2011; UA090.000056 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - UEP 217: Youth Violence in America: A Seminar for Policy Development, 2000 -- Spring 2004; UA090.000057 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - UEP 219: Urban Economics and Social Policy, Spring 2005; UA090.000058 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - UEP 221: Climate Change Policy, Planning and Action, Spring 2006 -- Spring 2010; UA090.000059 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - UEP 225: Community Engagement, Summer 2014; UA090.000060 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - UEP 222: Biotechnology: Social and Environmental Issues, Spring 2003 -- Spring 2009; UA090.000061 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - UEP 222-01: Biotechnology: Social and Environmental Issues, Spring 2009; UA090.000062 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - UEP 223: Fundamentals of U.S. Agriculture, Fall 2000 -- Fall 2004; UA090.000063 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - UEP 230: Negotiation, Mediation and Dispute Resolution, Fall 2002 -- Fall 2014; UA090.000064 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - UEP 232: Introduction to GIS for Urban and Environmental Analysis, 2002 -- Spring 2012; UA090.000065 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - UEP 233-01: Regional Planning: Tools and Techniques, Spring 2009; UA090.000066 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - UEP 233: Advanced GIS, Spring 2005; UA090.000067 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - UEP 234-01: Qualitative Analysis for Planning and Public Policy, Fall 2013; UA090.000068 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - UEP 240: Social Welfare Policy in the U.S.: History and Current Debates, Fall 2001 -- Fall 2013; UA090.000069 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - UEP 242: Race, Class, and Public Policy, Spring 2000 -- Fall 2005; UA090.000070 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - UEP 250: Perspectives on Urban and Environmental Policy, Fall 1983 -- Fall 2013; UA090.000071 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - UEP 251: Economics for Planning and Policy Analysis, Fall 1984 -- Fall 2010; UA090.000072 (Box 4, Folder 57)